Guide to the Walter Freeman, Class of 1916, Yale College, Photograph Albums Documenting Life at Yale
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Volume III
  - Page 36
    - 771. Bowl [excavation] (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Page 37
    - 772. Rogers [in single shell] (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 773. Lippincott - 1912 Olympics (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 774. Bouin (killed 1915) - 1912 Olympics (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 775. The Elihu Yale following the races (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 776. Platt, Adams - 1912 Olympics (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 777. Rose (died 1915) - 1912 Olympics (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 778-80. [Working in shells at New London] (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Page 38
    - 781. Junior four-oar, 1913 - Blackburn as coxswain (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 782. [Working in shell] (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 783. [In shell in front of Boathouse] (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 784. Latimer (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 785. Chism (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 786. Gianini in coaching launch run by A.B. Darling, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 787. Crew (duplicate of picture 788) (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 788. Crocker, Denegre, Rogers, Sturtevant, Harrison (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 789. Same crew, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - 790. [Two crews] (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Page 39
    - 791. Oxford bumping races (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 792. Gianini (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 793. Cornish, Zahnen, Whitmag, Enwright, Mute, Burnett, Wohler, Wilson, Hadley (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 794. Intercollegiate Champion Swimmers, 1913 - McAleenan, Roberts, Smits, Hoadley, Summers, Harper, Wilson, Mayer (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 795. Fitzpatrick and Denegre - [two-oar shell] (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 796. [Crew working in shell] (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 797. Oxford races (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 798. Baseball team on crew picnic [in launch] (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 799. Crew on same picnic - Hobson, Coe, Sheldon, Cushman (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Page 40
    - 800. [Crew working] (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 801. 1917 Freshmen in 1914 - Mayer, Dartlen, Coe, Hearn, Harriman, Atkins (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 802. McLane, Appleton, Ropp, Stillman, Sheldon, Nixon, Coe, Smith (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 803-04. [Crews working] (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 805. Harrison, Coe, Denegre, Sheldon, Titus, Rogers, Low, Gilfillen, McLane (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 806. Second Sophomore [Crew], Spring 1914 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - 807. [Crew working] (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Page 41
    - 808. Harrison, Suanders, Wallace, Lomas (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - 809. Lushman, Harrison, Coe, Lane, Bomitt, Klein, Titus, Donnelly, Denegre, Acheson, Meyer (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - 810-11. [Crews practicing] (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - 812. Rogers, Snowden (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - 813. [Crew putting shell in water] -- Gilfillen, McLane (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - 814. [Group in a pool - water polo?] (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - 815. Corinthian Yacht Club at Morris Cove (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Page 42
    - 816. Rogers, Titus, Sheldon, Crocker, Low, Windwall (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - 817. Float on the day of the races (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - 818. 1913 Harvard Crew (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - 819. English Crew (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - 820. Water Polo practice (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - 821. English Crew (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - 822. [Crew at practice] (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Page 43
    - 823. First Dunham Varsity - 1912 Fall Regatta - Shepard, Snowden, Titus, Ross, Stephenson, Penman, Gore, Burgee, Cushman (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - 824. First Varsity - Spring 1914-- McLane, Metleney, Titus, Low, Harrison, Appleton, Rogers, Sheldon, Coe (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - 825. Baseball picnic on the sound (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - 826. Ransom, Bunker, Vanholt, Cornish, Zanner, Gaillard (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - 827. On the day of the Spring Regatta, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - 828. Breaking ice (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - 829. Spring Regatta, 1912 - Second Fresh winning (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - 830. [Putting shell in water] Cumman, Begree, Penman, Stephenson, Ross, Gore, Shepard, Snowden (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - 831. Dickey, Munson Wohler, Hume, Schwalte, Hoadley (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Page 44
    - 832. Picnic 1915 - Stroke - Harvard (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - 833. [Oxford Crew] (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - 834. Barnum, Snowden, Coe, Philbin, Burgee, McHenry, Freeman, Denegre, Gore (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - 835. [Crew working] (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - 836. Tossing the shell at Red Top (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - 837. Leland Stanford Girls Crew (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Page 45
    - 838. Gaillard, winner of single scull race (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - 839-41. [Crew] (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - 842. 1917 Freshman [crew] -James, Saward, White (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - 843. First Juniors, first Seniors, first Sophomores- Spring 1914 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Page 46
    - 844. Barnum, Snowden, Lippincott, Penman, Jenkinson, Philbin, Denegre, Plimpton, Gore (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - 845. Moor, Gifillan, Denegre, Rogers, Sturtevant, Ross, Jenkinson, Meyer, Cushman (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - 846. Unidentified (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - 847. First Dunham Varsity, Fall 1912 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - 848. First Fresh, Spring 1912 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - 849. Tossing the shell on the back float (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - 850. [Crew] (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - 851. Water polo team - Braden, Steiner, unidentified, VonHolt, Mayer, Smith, Harper (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - 852. First Sheff Freshmen - Fall 1912 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Page 47
    - 853. Whitney [Olympics 1912] (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - 854-55. [Olympics 1912] (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - 856. Rose [Olympics 1912] (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - 857-58. [Olympics 1912] (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - 859. [Tennis] (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - 860. [Cabanas on wheels at seashore] (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - 861. [Antics at a game] (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Page 48
    - 862. Brown game [football] 1912 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - 863. Banjo club rehearsal, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - 864. Scroll and Key singing - Tompkins, Donaldson, Haynes (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - 865. A 1913 spring concert by the Orchestra (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - 866. Duplicate of picture 638 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - 867. [A pageant] (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Page 49
    - 868. [Hurdle jumpers at the Olympics] (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 869. Dual meet with Princeton, 1914, Shedden, Potter (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 870. [Olympics] (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 871. Mc Donald [Olympics] (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 872. Duplicate of picture 868 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 873. [Olympics] (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 874. [Baseball] -Watrous, Hunter, Hover, Campbell, Reilly, Middlebrook, Cornish, Vaughn, Walsh (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 875. [Olympics--end of race] (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 876. The Marathon (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Page 50
    - 877. [Rifle shooting] (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 878. Lincoln Beachy at Yale Field, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 879. Dressed as a woman (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 880. Duplicate picture 878 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 881. [Rifle shooting] (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 882. Duplicate of picture 881 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - 883. [Rifle shooting] (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Page 51
    - 884. [Tennis] (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 885. [Tennis]--R.C. Gates, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 886. [Tennis] (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 887. [Tennis]--Cunningham (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 888. [Tennis]--A.H. Man, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 889. [Tennis] (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 890. [Tennis]--R.N. Williams, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 891-93. [Tennis] (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Page 52
    - 894-95. [Tennis]--Man (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 896. [Tennis]--Harvard tennis team entering courts, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 897. R. Pierce, 1916 --[Golf] (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 898-99. [Tennis] (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 900. [Group from tennis team] (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 901. Field hockey at Bryn Mawr (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 903. [Diablo?] (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 904. J. Spaulding [police] (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - 905. [Tennis]--Stoddard (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Page 53
    - 906-07. [Pole vault] (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 908. Capt. Samuels, 1913, Flash at Y500 [gymnastics] (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 909. [Shotput] (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 910. Arnold, Stackpole, Dunn, Swihart, Smith, Herman (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 911. 1913 spring [track] meet, Willets, Rosener (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 912. Sprinters in Cage--Cowles, Cornall, Mack (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 913. [Hurdles in rain] (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 914. Capt. A. Wilson [swimming A] (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 915. [Group of 5 athletes] (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 916. [Rave, track] (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Page 54
    - 917. [Long jump] (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 918. Overton (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 919. [Football team], Roos, Turtle, Downey (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 920. [Swimmers about to dive] (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 921. [Track] (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 922. Gardiner 1912, Mack, National Championships, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 923. Potter [hurdles] (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 924. [Track] (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 925. Soccer team in Cage (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - 926. [Track] (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Page 55
    - 927-28. [Track] (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 929. [Track]--W. M. Oler 1916 at Harvard (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 930. [Track]--Brown 1915S (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 931. [Track] (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 932. [Track]--R.J. Douglas 1914 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 933. [Track] (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 934. [Track]--Wilke (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 935. [Track]--Chism (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 936. [Track]--Potter, Shelden (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 937. [Track] (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 938. [Track]--MacDonald (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Page 56
    - 939. [Track]--Oler, Rerell, fall 1912 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 940. [Track]--Roos (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 941. [Jump practice in Cage] (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 942. [Track] (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 943. [Track]--Avery (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - 944. [Track]--Ricketts (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Page 57
    - 945. [Track] (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - 946. [Track] (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - 947. [Track]--Marr, Gurney, Keeler (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - 948. [Track]--Wilkie (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - 949. [Track]--1914 fall, 440, Walker, M. Orr (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - 950. [Track]--Ricketts, Cornell, Ainsworth, Moore (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - 951. [Track]--Loughridge (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - 952. [Track]--Sheldon, Potter (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Page 58
    - 953. Finish of mile, spring 1913, Knapp 1915, Smith 1915S (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - 954. [Track]--Yale-Princeton, 1914, Willwts, Potter. Sheldon (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - 955. [Track]--Poucher, nearly a record (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - 956. [Track]--Overton (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - 957. [Track]--Potter, Sheldon (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - 958. [Track] (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Page 59
    - 959. [Track] (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 960. Omega Lamda Chi celebration with Whiffenpoofs, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 961. Last Brown game celebration (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 962. The water wagon, Omega Lamda Chi, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 963. Duplicate of picture 961 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 964. Whiffenpoof-Mohican baseball game, Omega Lamda Chi (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 965. Duplicate of picture 961 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 966. [Antics involved in Omega Lamda Chi] (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Page 60
    - 967. Freshmen Mandolin tuning up, Russell, Barney, Baber (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 968. Psi Upsilon having its picture taken in front of Tomb, Nov. 1913 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 969. Boys Club show, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 970. [Brown game celebration], Lewis, Perkins (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 971. Freshman Mandolin Club, Welch, Babor, Penny, Cassard, Russell, Sutherland, Proctor, Meyer, Manning, Shore, Hapgood (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 972. Calcium light night, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 973. [Group of students working] (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 974. [Student baseball] (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Page 61
    - 975. Steady Now, [giant camera set up on the corner of Chapel and College Streets] (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 976. The players' entrance to the Bowl [under construction] (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 977. Walter Camp (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 978. 1914 seniors playing Diabolo, Mendelson, Harbison, Marting, Cooney (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 979. Omega Lamda Chi, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 980. [Group with suitcases] (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 981. Soccer with a sponge, Wilson, Caldwell, Grant (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 982. Topps, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Page 62
    - 983. J. F. Freeman on pole on Green after a crowd, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 984. Social service tour of the Bowery, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 985. [Group with bags, in front of Osborn] (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 986. Yale Station at morning mail (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 987. Miller, McConnal, Grabes, Eckman, Scarlet Fever scare (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 988. Princetonian, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 989. [Snake march] (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 990. [Golf] (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Page 63
    - 991. Tap Day, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - 992. Omega Lamda Chi day, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - 993. Dramat movie taking at Phelps (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - 994. Diabolo, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - 995. [Costumer revelers] (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Page 64
    - 996. Spring 1913, watching performance of squirrel and cat (see pictures 477, 579, 580) (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - 997. Prexi beats the choir out of Chapel, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - 998. Watching election returns in the Oval at night, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - 999. Omega Lamda Chi address by H.R. Hawley, Y 1914 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - 1000. C.J. Coe, 1913 and M.A. Farr, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Page 65
    - 1001. The Stage, Lyman Guernsey, Patterson (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1002. Parade at Princeton (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1003. A fire in the hold of the good ship Schooner [parade], 1913 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1004. Hiram Bingham's Peruvian expedition tents aired in front of Herrick, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1005. Thanksgiving --julification in Dwight (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1006. Springtime for 1914 seniors (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1007. [Dramat movie taking] (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1008. [Large group] (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1009. 1915 seniors [portrait taking] (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Page 66
    - 1010. Freshman Mandolin trials, 1912, Cary, Ricketts, Russell, Pratt, Freeman, Wyler, Fish, Perkins, Jones, Pierce (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1011. "Pooch" Donovan, Harvard trainer (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1012. Woodfire talk in Byers (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1013. Pushball at Illinois (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1014. Tops, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1015. Gregory lecturing to a geological expedition (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1016. [Group in front of Taft] (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1017. [Diabolo] (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 1018. Calcium light night (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Page 67
    - 1019-21. Truck carrying Whiffs to Brown game, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - 1022. Omega Lamda Chi, 1913, at Tillman (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - 1023. Whiffenpoofs having their picture taken, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - 1024. News vs. Heelers bicycle polo (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - 1025. [Parade] (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Page 68
    - 1026. Whiffenpoofs photographed in Vanderbilt Court, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - 1027. 1912 spring competition for the News Heelers from 1915 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - 1028. [Man in slicker on wharf] (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - 1029. C. T. Coe testing fliers (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - 1030. [men on fence] (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - 1031. China in Yale, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - 1032. Duplicate picture 1027 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Page 69
    - 1033. Listening to campus concert, spring 1913 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - 1034. Oval, April 1913 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - 1035. [Group on campus] (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - 1036. Jim Donnally Camp, Farr (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - 1037. [Campus antics] (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Page 70
    - 1038. Football crowd at gate of old field (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - 1039. H.A. Farr --Tute (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - 1040. Cheering the crew off the Ferry, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - 1041. Baseball squad about to start south, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - 1042. [Freight cars filled with people] (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - 1043. [Man on ship] (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - 1044. Duplicate of picture 1040 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Page 71
    - 1045. W. J. Freeman, cheering the crew of 1913 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 1046. Harner leads the cheering (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 1047. Cheering crew off (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 1048. Whiffenpoof fun, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 1049. Speech by Hadley (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 1050. [Competition] (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Page 72
    - 1051. 1914 class panorama from Lawrence (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 1052. H.R. (Boz) Hawlay making his address on students --I don't remember your face but your breath is very familiar (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 1053. Rosers car ran into fruit stand (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 1054. Whiffs vs. Mohican baseball game on Omega Lamda Chi (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 1055. [Person at desk] (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 1056. [Rifle club] (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Volume IV
  - Page 1
    - 1057. Off for the weekend (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - 1058. 1915S junior prom 1915, Feb 9 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - 1059. [Large group] (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Page 2
    - 1060. Art Illinois rush (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - 1061. Morning mail (Oval) (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - 1062. [Group] (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Page 3
    - 1063. Alumni University Day, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - 1064. Marching to football practice, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - 1065. Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Page 4
    - 1066. Birmingham, Wood, Gross, Felty, Morris, Wiles, Gilbert, Wyer, Polhamus (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - 1067. Going to 8:30's in winter (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - 1068. [Dramat movies] (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Page 5
    - 1069. Denegre Prexy, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - 1070. Nickalls, Camp, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - 1071. [sunset with boats and crew on river] (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - 1072. Taft, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Page 6
    - 1073. McLane, Morse, Low, Meyer, Sturtevant, Sheldon, Denegre, Wiman [crew] (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - 1074. McNaughton (killed flying 3/13/18), Meyer (wounded in action Belgium, 1915), Sturtevant (killed flying 1918), Sheldon, Low, Gilfillan, Hurne, McLane, [crew] (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - 1075. [Old Campus from Taft(?)] (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - 1076. Seth Low II (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Page 7
    - 1077. Undertakers at work Launsbury Funeral (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - 1078. The Ordeal [Play operation] (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - 1079. Roberts, Eastman, Ocumpaugh (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - 1080. May 1916 (play) (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Page 8
    - 1081. Fire in New Haven yards (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - 1082. Lounsbury funeral (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - 1083. Springtime, play (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - 1084. Academic procession, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Page 9
    - 1085. Baseball team in Washington, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - 1086. [Old Campus in snow] (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - 1087. [Pond in winter] (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - 1088. Jones, Eastman, Hoff, Hyde, Welch, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Page 10
    - 1089. 1915 (play) (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - 1090. Berkeley Oval, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - 1091. Steamboat wharf (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - 1092. [Old Campus during inclement weather] (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Page 11
    - 1093. Harvard meet, 1914, Willets, Shelden (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - 1094. Harvard team 1915, tennis (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - 1095. Traps, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - 1096. Freshmen, 1914 [baseball] (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Page 12
    - 1097. Johnstone [pole vault] (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - 1098. Shelden [football] (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - 1099. Sutherland, Beebe, Cart, 1914 [surveyors] (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - 1100. Boome, Grinnell, Saylor, Brice, Courant relay team (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - 1101. Thompson, Barker, Phelps, Crawford (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Page 13
    - 1102. English class in Byers, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - 1103. Building St. Anthony, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - 1104. T.M. Osborn warden, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - 1105. [Winter in front of --the Maples--] (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - 1106. University central in Oval (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - 1107. College Street (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - 1108. Glacier Ball, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - 1109. Campus north from Vanderbilt (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Page 14
    - 1110. Osborn lab, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - 1111. Newberry Organ in Woolsey, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - 1112. Van Gates, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - 1113. Libraries, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Page 15
    - 1114. W.J. Freeman, Y 1916 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - 1115. Bill Wiser at 68, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - 1116. Betts, Walden, Ainsworth, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - 1117. Baccalaureate sermon, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - 1118. Academic procession, 1917, 40 men back from first Officer's camp at Plattsburgh (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Page 16
    - 1119. Yale Naval Reserve, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - 1120. Sheff skates [scooter] (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - 1121. Yale Pageant, Oct 1916 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - 1122. Easton (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - 1123. Hadley, Pershing, Brown, Commencement, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - 1124. Intercollegiates, 1914 [cross-country] (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - 1125. Scovil, Ainsworth, Knowles, LeGore, Backfield, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Page 17
    - 1126. McLennan, Goodley, Davenmuehle (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - 1127. Goodwin (killed flying, July 1915) (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - 1128. Washburn, Enwright (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - 1129. Second crew, May, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - 1130. First crew, Easter (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Page 18
    - 1131. [crew at practice] (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - 1132. Glacier Ball in Connecticut Hall, Newton, Chism, Stewart, Brady, Goodwin, Miller, Innes, Tefft (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - 1133. Hampton, Aldrich, Caldwell, Torson (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Page 19
    - 1134. Washburn, Levy (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - 1135. Boilers under gym (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - 1136. Phelps from library, May 1915 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - 1137. Weekend trip (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - 1138. Johnes, Hunter, Washburn, Lee (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - 1139. Phenix, A. Proctor (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Page 20
    - 1140. Wright court (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - 1141. Brick row, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - 1142. 1914 [on fence] (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - 1143. 9:30 PM, 1915, exam time (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Page 21
    - 1144. St. Anthony, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - 1145. Fagan, Enwright, Hopkins, Lloyd (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - 1146. L. Miller, 1916 [rolling hoop down College Street] (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - 1147. Willard, Eastman, Thompson, Proctor, Brady, White, Polhamus, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Page 22
    - 1148. Eastman, Vaugh, Tighe, Rumelin, Porter, Titlmann, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - 1149. Snow, inner campus (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - 1150. Yale movies, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - 1151. Midnight concert (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Page 23
    - 1152. Hogan float afire, Omega Lamda Chi, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - 1153. Pounding for worms, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - 1154. Mexico parade, Easter, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - 1155. Bethany picnic (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - 1156. Tap day (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - 1157. [Connecticut Hall] (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Page 24 BLANK (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Page 25
    - 1158. Baseball--Pompelly, Stevens, Hanes, C. Hunter, Reilly, Harpham, Middlebrook, Falsey, Brown, Goodell, Harvey, Rumelin, Y. Stevens (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1159. [Baseball]--Football men lined up to see a baseball game (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1160. [Baseball]--Innes (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1161. [Baseball]--Pompelly (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - 1162. [Baseball]--Pompelly scoring on Southern trip, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 96)